greenopia.com 2009-06-20

# G r e e n o p i a

**Greenopia TM / The Green Media Group, LLC PRIVACY POLICY  
**  
At Greenopia, we respect your privacy. That is why we want you to know how we protect the privacy and security of the information we collect about you on our website. Please take a moment to review the paragraphs below, which describe our privacy and security practices. Visiting our website is your consent to these practices. 

**Information We Collect  
** Greenopia may collect personal information about you and non-personal information about your visit when you access our website. When you register with Greenopia, you will be asked to provide a valid email address, a user name and your zip code. Other personally identifiable information that we may collect includes user-submitted information such as name, age, gender and physical address as well as statements, information, and/or pictures you post to our website. 

The non-personal information we collect includes the domain name of the site providing you with Internet access, the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your browser type and version, the operating system your computer is running, and other site visit data pertaining to the pages you view, information you search for, and the average time spent on our website. 

We also collect and store information about you and your visits to our site using cookies and/or web beacons. Greenopia will set a cookie when you select a geographic region as your default region. And we will set a cookie that identifies you when you log in as a registered user. One of the primary purposes of cookies is your convenience and to help you save time. For example, cookies are necessary to maintain your preferences and to allow you to freely move from page to page within our site. These cookies can be reset to change your default region or other user preferences when necessary. You can decide if and how your computer will accept cookies by configuring your preferences option within your web browser. If you choose to decline cookies, however, some of the functionality of the Greenopia site may be impaired. Web beacons, also known as clear gifs and web bugs, allow us to recognize a cookie on your computer when you view a web page or e-mail. These electronic images help us measure the effectiveness of our online advertising and/or e-mail campaigns by, for example, counting the number of individuals who visit our website or the number of individuals who open or act upon an e-mail message. 

**Using Your Information  
** Greenopia does not sell, rent, trade, use, or otherwise share your personal information without your consent except in accordance with this policy. 

Only registered users that have accepted our Terms of Use may place content on our website. If you create a personal profile or contribute to listings or forums on our website, the information you voluntarily make available (e.g., comments, profiles, pictures or screen names) will be accessible by the general public and may be shared freely. Greenopia allows this information to be displayed for the sole purpose of facilitating interaction among our users and visitors. We cannot control misuse of publicly-available information by others. We therefore urge you to exercise caution when posting information to message boards or other public forums available on our website. 

Personal information that we collect about you during the registration process, such as your name, email address, and zip code, is used for authentication, to communicate with you regarding technical issues, to send you our monthly newsletter, and to help us focus the information displayed on our website on that which is most appropriate to your geographic region. We also use this information to notify you about special offers that may be forthcoming or products and services offered by our affiliates or other third parties that relate to your specific interests, hobbies, or other information you have provided. To maintain this website and for internal business purposes, we may share your personal information with our affiliates, business partners, and others who do work for us such as service providers, vendors, contractors and agents, including information technology service providers. 

If you provide your complete physical address, this information will be used to enable a smarter connection to GoogleMaps TM and to help us respond to your requests that require us to contact you by mail. 

Non-personal information about your site visits, information about your personal interests that you provide, and certain demographic information is used in the aggregate to better understand our entire audience. This information helps us increase the functionality and user-friendliness of our website and better tailor the site to our visitors' needs. Greenopia may share aggregated data with third parties for these and other purposes, such as advertising. 

To the extent permitted by law, any information (personal and non-personal) regarding the use of our websites may be disclosed to government authorities or third parties pursuant to a legal request, subpoena, or other legal process. We may also use or disclose your information as permitted by law to fight fraud or protect the safety, security, property, or livelihood of Greenopia, our customers, our website, or its users. 

**Opting Out of Communications From Us  
** While many of our users appreciate the benefits that come with online registration, we respect your individual right to control your information. If you do not wish to receive communications from us, or our affiliates, you can uncheck the box that allows us to use your information for this purpose when your information is collected. You may also email us at info@greenopia.com or click on the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any email communication from us to indicate that do not wish to receive future communications. 

**Children's Information  
** Greenopia's website is a general audience site and does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 without verifiable parental consent. If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide personally identifiable information of any kind whatsoever. 

**Security  
** This site uses standard security measures to prevent the loss, misuse, or alteration of the information under our control. We take standard precautions to insure that member account information remains private. And we use commercially reasonable measures (not necessarily the latest or most advanced technology) to protect the information stored within our databases. Greenopia does not guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. 

**Third Party Advertisements  
** Greenopia or its advertisers may elect to use third-party advertising companies to serve ads onto our website. For example, Greenopia currently allows Life Balance Media LLC ("Lime") to display advertisements on our website. Lime and any other third party advertising companies Greenopia may use are subject to their own privacy policies, not ours. In the course of serving these advertisements, the third-party advertising companies may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser and may use web beacons or similar technologies. The third party advertisers use the cookies and web beacons to collect data about site visitors (for example, they can identify a repeat visitor, geographic location of a visitor and ads viewed), but this information is not personally identifiable. However, we do not have access to third party cookies or web beacons or any information that they may contain. 

Because these companies may serve advertisements on many different websites, they may be able to compile information over time about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements they display. These companies may use this information to make predictions about your characteristics or preferences and to display targeted advertisements that they believe may be of interest to you. They may also associate this information with your subsequent visit, purchase or other activity on participating advertisers' websites in order to determine the effectiveness of the advertisements. Any such data is collected on an anonymous basis and is not linked to specific identifiable individuals. 

To reiterate, third-party advertising companies such as Lime and any advertisements displayed on the Greenopia site to which you may link, are subject to their own privacy policies (see Third-Party Privacy Policies below). 

**Third-Party Privacy Policies  
** To help you and provide you as much information as possible, this website may contain links to other websites. This privacy policy applies only to information collected on the Greenopia website. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave this website and to read the privacy policy of each website you visit before providing any personal information. 

**Changes of Control  
** Greenopia reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of a change of control, such as the sale of Greenopia or substantially all of its assets. . 

**Changes To Our Policy  
** Your continued use of our website constitutes your agreement to this privacy policy and any updates. Greenopia reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to make changes to this privacy policy. Any changes will be posted here and will be apparent from the revision date located at the bottom of this policy. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy policy to stay informed about how we are protecting the personal information we collect. 

**Asking Questions  
** If you have questions or concerns about our privacy practices or data use, or wish to change your options, please email us at [info@greenopia.com](mailto:info@greenopia.com). 

Published on  Greenopia.com TM   
Privacy Policy   
Revised December 2007
